<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TwoActivities CodingChallenge</string>
    <string name="button_two_label">Text Two</string>
    <string name="button_one_label">Text One</string>
    <string name="button_three_label">Text Three</string>
    <string name="article_one_heading">World Cup 2019: Rohit Sharma, Yuzvendra Chahal power India to opening win over South Africa</string>
    <string name="article_one_content"><b>Rohit Sharma</b> steered India to a 6-wicket victory in their opening match of the 2019 Cricket World Cup after Yuzvendra Chahal and Jasprit Bumrah restricted South Africa to 227 for 9. The Proteas have now lost all their 3 matches so far in the tournament. Rohit remained unbeaten on 122 as India reached the target with 15 balls to spare.\n\nIndia made a nervous start as they chased a middling target in overcast conditions. Rohit Sharma and Shikhar Dhawan prodded and poked at deliveries outside the off-stump before Dhawan finally played at a Kagiso Rabada delivery he should have left well alone.\n\nVirat Kohli, the world\'s best batsman, was tested by Chris Morris and Rabada. He was no where near his fluent best but Kohli decided to bide his time. However, Kohli perished for 18 when Andile Phehlukwayo found steep bounce and he tried to steer it away - instead all Kohli managed was a thick edge and South Africa wicketkeeper Quinton de Kock held on to a sensational catch.\n\nAt 54 for 2 in the 16th over with the ball doing a bit and the South African pacers looking dangerous, India were in a spot of bother. Another wicket at that stage could have put the South Africans on top but Rohit Sharma and India's new No.4 KL Rahul had other ideas.\n\nAt the end, the 227 for 9 was not enough only because South Africa had no answer to the genius of Rohit Sharma.\n\n</string>
    <string name="article_two_heading">Chandrababu Naidu writes letter to CM YS Jagan over Praja Vedika</string>
    <string name="article_two_content">Amaravati: The TDP national president and former CM Nara Chandrababu Naidu have written a letter to Chief Minister YS Jagan Mohan Reddy.\n\nThrough the letter, the TDP supremo said, as you are aware, the Praja Vedika is being used as the facility for conducting various meetings and meeting the visitors, by declaring it as CM residence annexe, since there was hardly any open space in the residence chosen by me.\n\nPost Assembly Elections 2019, following my demitting of CM office, I have decided to retain the same private house, as per the agreed terms and conditions of the private owner of the property.\n\nSince the Praja Vedika is located beside my existing residence, I am planning to retain it for my official use. As you are aware I have been chosen as the leader of the Telugu Desam Legislature Party, to discharge my responsibilities as the leader of the opposition.I wish to continue the same arrangement, that the Praja Vedika be declared as the residence annexe of the leader of the opposition, to facilitate me to meet legislators, visitors, common public and discharge my duties.The YSRCP has achieved landslide victory by winning 151 Assembly and 22 Parliament seats and YS Jagan has sworn-in as Chief Minister on 30 May in Vijayawada.\n\n</string>
    <string name="article_three_heading">AP EAMCET Result 2019: Andhra Council declares EAMCET results today, here\'s how to check</string>
    <string name="article_three_content">AP EAMCET Result 2019: APSCHE has declared the AP EAMCET Result 2019 on the official website of the council- apsche.org. Apart from the official website, the students can also check their results on- sche.ap.gov.in and eamcet.tshe.gov.in.\n\nThe Andhra Pradesh State Council of Higher Education (APSCHE) has declared the Andhra Pradesh Engineering, Agricultural and Medical Common Entrance Test (AP EAMCET) results today. The AP EAMCET results were expected to be out at 11.30 AM on the official website of the council- apsche.org, however, as per latest reports, the results were delayed but are announced now. Apart from the official website, the students can also check their results on- sche.ap.gov.in and eamcet.tshe.gov.in.\n\nA rank-wise merit list of students will be put up on the official website along with the name and hall ticket number of the candidates. This year, the AP EAMCET exam was conducted between April 20 and 24. The council has already released the response sheets for the AP EAMCET examination 2019.\n\n</string>
</resources>
